import { ILessonQuestion } from '../services/lesson.service';

export const VIETNAMESE_QUESTIONS: ILessonQuestion[] = [
  {answer: 'a.m4a', lessonUnit: 'A-a', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'aw.m4a', lessonUnit: 'Ă-ă', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'aa.m4a', lessonUnit: 'Â-â', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'b.m4a', lessonUnit: 'B-b', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'c.m4a', lessonUnit: 'C-c', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'd.m4a', lessonUnit: 'D-d', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'dd.m4a', lessonUnit: 'Đ-đ', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'e.m4a', lessonUnit: 'E-e', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'ee.m4a', lessonUnit: 'Ê-ê', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'g.m4a', lessonUnit: 'G-g', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'h.m4a', lessonUnit: 'H-h', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'i.m4a', lessonUnit: 'I-i', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'k.m4a', lessonUnit: 'K-k', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'l.m4a', lessonUnit: 'L-l', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'm.m4a', lessonUnit: 'M-m', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'n.m4a', lessonUnit: 'N-n', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'o.m4a', lessonUnit: 'O-o', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'oo.m4a', lessonUnit: 'Ô-ô', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'ow.m4a', lessonUnit: 'Ơ-ơ', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'p.m4a', lessonUnit: 'P-p', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'q.m4a', lessonUnit: 'Q-q', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'r.m4a', lessonUnit: 'R-r', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 's.m4a', lessonUnit: 'S-s', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 't.m4a', lessonUnit: 'T-t', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'u.m4a', lessonUnit: 'U-u', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'uw.m4a', lessonUnit: 'Ư-ư', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'v.m4a', lessonUnit: 'V-v', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'x.m4a', lessonUnit: 'X-x', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'y.m4a', lessonUnit: 'Y-y', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'sac.m4a', lessonUnit: '/-Cá', question: 'what-is-character.m4a'},
  {answer: 'quyen.m4a', lessonUnit: '\\-Bà', question: 'what-is-character.m4a'},
  {answer: 'hoi.m4a', lessonUnit: '?-Bổ', question: 'what-is-character.m4a'},
  {answer: 'nga.m4a', lessonUnit: '~-Bão', question: 'what-is-character.m4a'},
  {answer: 'nan.m4a', lessonUnit: '.-Dạ', question: 'what-is-character.m4a'},
];

export const ENGLISH_QUESTIONS: ILessonQuestion[] = [
  {answer: 'A.m4a', lessonUnit: 'A-a', question: 'how-you-spell-that.m4a'},
  {answer: 'B.m4a', lessonUnit: 'B-b', question: 'how-you-spell-that.m4a'},
  {answer: 'C.m4a', lessonUnit: 'C-c', question: 'how-you-spell-that.m4a'},
  {answer: 'D.m4a', lessonUnit: 'D-d', question: 'how-you-spell-that.m4a'},
  {answer: 'E.m4a', lessonUnit: 'E-e', question: 'how-you-spell-that.m4a'},
  {answer: 'F.m4a', lessonUnit: 'F-f', question: 'how-you-spell-that.m4a'},
  {answer: 'G.m4a', lessonUnit: 'G-g', question: 'how-you-spell-that.m4a'},
  {answer: 'H.m4a', lessonUnit: 'H-h', question: 'how-you-spell-that.m4a'},
  {answer: 'I.m4a', lessonUnit: 'I-i', question: 'how-you-spell-that.m4a'},
  {answer: 'J.m4a', lessonUnit: 'J-j', question: 'how-you-spell-that.m4a'},
  {answer: 'K.m4a', lessonUnit: 'K-k', question: 'how-you-spell-that.m4a'},
  {answer: 'L.m4a', lessonUnit: 'L-l', question: 'how-you-spell-that.m4a'},
  {answer: 'M.m4a', lessonUnit: 'M-m', question: 'how-you-spell-that.m4a'},
  {answer: 'N.m4a', lessonUnit: 'N-n', question: 'how-you-spell-that.m4a'},
  {answer: 'O.m4a', lessonUnit: 'O-o', question: 'how-you-spell-that.m4a'},
  {answer: 'P.m4a', lessonUnit: 'P-p', question: 'how-you-spell-that.m4a'},
  {answer: 'Q.m4a', lessonUnit: 'Q-q', question: 'how-you-spell-that.m4a'},
  {answer: 'R.m4a', lessonUnit: 'R-r', question: 'how-you-spell-that.m4a'},
  {answer: 'S.m4a', lessonUnit: 'S-s', question: 'how-you-spell-that.m4a'},
  {answer: 'T.m4a', lessonUnit: 'T-t', question: 'how-you-spell-that.m4a'},
  {answer: 'U.m4a', lessonUnit: 'U-u', question: 'how-you-spell-that.m4a'},
  {answer: 'V.m4a', lessonUnit: 'V-v', question: 'how-you-spell-that.m4a'},
  {answer: 'W.m4a', lessonUnit: 'W-w', question: 'how-you-spell-that.m4a'},
  {answer: 'X.m4a', lessonUnit: 'X-x', question: 'how-you-spell-that.m4a'},
  {answer: 'Y.m4a', lessonUnit: 'Y-y', question: 'how-you-spell-that.m4a'},
  {answer: 'Z.m4a', lessonUnit: 'Z-z', question: 'how-you-spell-that.m4a'},
];
